<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Sijun&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://jeffreysijuntan.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://jeffreysijuntan.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>jeffreysijuntan © 2019</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://jeffreysijuntan.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://jeffreysijuntan.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jeffreysijuntan.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jeffreysijuntan.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why join the navy if you can be a pirate?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi, I am Jeffrey Tan, a third-year undergrad at the University of Virginia majoring in computer science and mathematics. I grew up in Guangzhou, China, a city known as the origin of the language Cantonese. Unfortunately, although borned and raised in Guangzhou, I do not know how to speak Cantonese. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a researcher in computer vision. I worked at UVa Vision Lab under &lt;a href=&#34;http://vicenteordonez.com&#34;&gt;Professor Vicente Ordenez&lt;/a&gt;. We are working on
unsupervised learning of image representations through image patches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last summer I worked at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;lsquo;s natural language processing team. I helped build the entity linking system that process billions of posts on Facebook each day. I have always dreamed of serving the entire world with technology and working at Facebook was a realization of that dream. I am grateful for the friends I have made and the insights I have gained during my great time there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a brilliant bathroom singer and a not-so-bad guitar player. My journey of playing guitar is hugely inspired by Ed Sheeran, who can be perform like a whole band himself with just a guitar and a loop-pedal. I myself owns an Martin&#39;s Ed Sheeran Signature Guitar. Here is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bilibili.com/video/av39835314?from=search&amp;amp;seid=16579860154516860305&#34;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; of me singing Thinking out loud by Ed Sheeran.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;news&#34;&gt;News&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our research project report &lt;strong&gt;Selling Information for Competitive Buyers&lt;/strong&gt; for the class &lt;strong&gt;CS6501:Learning and Game Theory&lt;/strong&gt; is &lt;a href=&#34;files/CS6501_report.pdf&#34;&gt;out&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our Django website &lt;strong&gt;Cabville: A rideshare platform for UVa students&lt;/strong&gt; is up and deployed on &lt;a href=&#34;http://cabville.herokuapp.com/&#34;&gt;heroku&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
